GUR SHALEV

Software Developer

- +972 544288970
- shalevgurl@gmail.com
- m www.linkedin.com/in/gur-shalev
- https://github.com/shalevgurl
- https://shalevgur1.github.io/gurshalev.github.io/



LANGUAGES

- Hebrew
- English
- Spanish



SKILLS

- Python
- SQL
- MATLAB
- C#
- C++
- C
- Embedded
- JavaScript
- React
- HTML
- CSS
- Networks
- Web 3.0
- ICP
- Ethereum Dev
- Management
- Digital Marketing



TOOLS

- PyCharm
- PyChairiVSCode
- Wireshark
- MATLAB IDE
- MAILADIL
- git
- GitHub



AWARDS

ISRAELI CYBER CHAMPIONSHIP

2019 | 3rd place national

HIGH SCHOOL OUTSTANDING CERTIFICATE

Node.is

PostgreSQL

2019 | Outstanding Certificate for highest achievements and social engagement

COMANDER COURSE

2021 | 1st place Battalion, 2nd place Unit



VOLUNTEERING

COMMUNITY AND FARMING

2024 | Support local community in enhancing agricultural capabilities in Colombia's tropical Andes region. Worked as a Customer Application Engineer at a startup specializing in RF sensor technology.

A veteran from the IDF's Intelligence Gathering Combat unit, as a commander and combat medic. I am a fast and self-learner, ambitious, hard worker, and passionate about my work.

Driven by excellence, always looking forward for new challenges and acquiring more knowledge. I am fond of combining my three passions: people, computer science, and music (play piano and

A

saxophone).

WORK EXPERIENCE

Vayyar LTD | 2023 - 2024

Customer Application Engeneering

- Took part in developing and building applications for clients in a variety of industries with a focus on the Automotive industry.
- Defect & Bug Tracking, and Debugging.
- Developing and maintaining Embedded systems.
- Visiting clients abroad for support and guidance.
- Product demonstration and public speaking.
- Developing and maintaining APIs and SDKs.



MILITARY SERVICE

Combat Commander School | 2021 - 2022

Squad Commander

- Working under pressure.
- Appling teaching methods, lesson planning, and public speaking.
- People management.

Operational Work | 2020 - 2021

Squad Commander

- Working with special technology equipment
- Excellent teamwork capabilities, cooperating with colleagues and officers.



WORK EXPERIENCE

CheckPoint LTD | 2019 - 2020

OA Engineer

- Operated different Software and Hardware tests on a variety of Check Point appliances and security servers.
- Self-Learning and independent internship.
- UI & Compatibility Testing.
- Performance, Load & Stress Testing



EDUCATION

Ammi Assaf high school | 2016 - 2019

- 5 pts. in Cyber Security and Networks.
- 5 pts. in Computer Science, Physics, Math, and English.
- Studied in Scientific and Technological leadership class.
- Social engagement certificate of excellence.

* Self Employed - Saxophone Player

Started a business for playing saxophone at weddings and parties. Applying digital marketing techniques for exposure, and client management.